Guide to the Heterosexual popular fiction collection, 1955-1992
Heterosexual popular fiction collection, 1955-1992
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Heterosexual popular fiction collection, 1955-1992
7690
71 v., comprising 1.6 cubic ft.
Printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Erotic and pornographic novels in the pulp paperback format on heterosexual subjects.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Erotic and pornographic novels in the pulp paperback format on heterosexual subjects.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Heterosexuals.; Popular literature.
Form and Genre Terms:
Erotica.; Pornography.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Books are listed alphabetically by author. Title, publisher, series and series number if applicable (-0- if not), and date are also given.
CONTAINER LIST
- Adrian, Jill. Mother's Hidden Room. Gloucestor Publishing Co., 1974 (Box 1)
- Anonymous. The Autobiography of a Flea. Carroll & Graf Publishers, 1983 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Beauty in the Birch. Blue Moon Books, 1989 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Blue Velvet. Grove Press, 1986 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Captured. Carroll & Graf Publishers, 1991 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. The Consumate Eveline. Carroll & Graf Publishers, 1992 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. The Days at Florville. Grove Press, 1983 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. The Gardens of the Night. Grove Press, 1985 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Harriet Marwood, Governess. Grove Press, 1986 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Jennifer: Book Eight. Dell Publishing, 1982 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. The Lustful Turk. Carroll & Graf Publishers, 1983 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Rosa Fielding: Victim of Lust. Carroll & Graf Publishers, 1983 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Seduced & Abandoned. Star Distributors, 1989 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Soul Slave. Star Distributors, 1989 (Box 4)
- Anonymous. Autobiography Of A Bellboy, The. (Box 5)
- Anonymous. Young But Bad and Other Stories. Pendulum Books, Inc., 1968 (Box 10)
- Arthur, Wallace. The Scandalous Scoundrel. Dominion Publishing Co., 1968 (Box 1)
- Avallone, Mike. All The Way. Tower Publications, Inc., 1960 (Box 5)
- Baker, Dorothy. Young Man With a Horn. Penguin Books, Inc., 1945 (Box 1)
- Baker, Randy. Darers Go First. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 8)
- Balmer, John. One Too Many. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 7)
- Barrett, Cliff. Scuttle World. Echelon Book Publishers, 1971 (Box 1)
- Bater, Peter. In A Lust Fashion. Swan Reader, 1956 (Box 7)
- Beam, L.M.. Carnal Delight. Carlyle Communications Inc., 1974 (Box 1)
- Beauchamp, Loren. Unwilling Sinner. Tower Publications, Inc., 1959 (Box 5)
- Bell, Steve. Venus Of Lesbos. Newsstand Library, Incorporated, 1961 (Box 7)
- Bennett, William. Nor Fears Of Hell. Fabian Books Publications, 1959 (Box 7)
- Black, Brian. Secrets, The. Softcover Library, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Blaine, Jud. Fling, The. Softcover Library, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Blake, Alex. Family Mistress. Rapture Books, 1965 (Box 8)
- Boots, Tiffany. Five Men. Grove Press, 1969 (Box 1)
- Brandel, Marc. Time Of The Fire, The. Bantam Books, Inc., 1955 (Box 5)
- Brandon, Ralph. One Violent Year. Fabian Books, 1959 (Box 1)
- Bravi, Roman. Prince of Pain. Eros Publishing Co., 1975 (Box 1)
- Britain, Sloane M.. Needle, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1959 (Box 6)
- Britt, Del. Rear-End Rapist. Eros Publishing, 1976 (Box 1)
- Brock, Rose. Tarn House. Avon Books Division, 1971 (Box 10)
- Brooks, Barbara. Campus Cat Pack. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 7)
- Brooks, Barbara. Hellcat. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 8)
- Brooks, Barbara. Handle With Care. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Brown, Wenzell. Sherry. Monarch Books, Inc., 1964 (Box 7)
- Busch, Niven. Duel In The Sun. Popular Library, 1947 (Box 5)
- Byram, George. Stronger Than Passion. Monarch Books, Inc., 1959 (Box 6)
- Calvet, Jean. Scandalous French Doctor. Bedside Books Incorporated, 1959 (Box 8)
- Carewe, S.C.. Students' Empty Bed Blues. Surrey House, 1971 (Box 1)
- Carson, Dave. Woman Hater. Tower Publications, 1960 (Box 5)
- Carson, Lee. Autobiography Of A Seductress. Novel Books, Inc., 1961 (Box 6)
- Cassell, Lucas J.. Teen Model. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 7)
- Cassill, R.V.. Dormitory Women. Lion Books, Inc., 1955 (Box 8)
- Castleman, Charles. Season Of Sin. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Chanslor, Roy. The Naked I. Popular Library, 1955 (Box 4)
- Christian, P.J.. Sex Show Sweetie. Eros Publishing, 1975 (Box 1)
- Clayton, Gina. Sweet and Sour Revenge. Pleasure Books, Inc., 1976 (Box 1)
- Clements, Mark. Handy-Man. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- Clements, Mark. Out Of Control. Tower Publications, 1956 (Box 9)
- Climax, Charlie*. Sex in the Crystal Ball. Peyote Press, 1969 (Box 1)
- Clubb, Stacey. Oddballs, The. Softcover Library, Inc., 1965 (Box 5)
- Cockford, Pat. Lick the Giggle Stick. Pussycat Publishing, 1969 (Box 1)
- Colette. Intimate Diary of a French Showgirl. Avon Publications, Inc., 1957 (Box 9)
- Comstock, J.C.. Sothern Belle. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 7)
- Covington, Ursula. The Protesting Wife. Tiburon House Publishing Co., 1973 (Box 1)
- Curtis, Brad. Man-Tamer. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 8)
- Davidson, John. Hot Cargo. Art Enterprises, Inc., 1961 (Box 6)
- Davis, Roger. Always Love A Stranger. Hillman Books, 1961 (Box 4)
- Dent, Lester. Cry at Dusk. Fawcett Publications, Inc., 1959 (Box 10)
- Diver, Dianne. Reverse Roles. Maverick Publishing Co., 1978 (Box 1)
- Douglas, Craig. Senior Prom. Chevron Publications, 1967 (Box 1)
- Dowling, Ben. The Erotic Voyage. New World Publishing Co. (Box 1)
- Draper, Jess. His For The Taking. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 6)
- Elliott, Bruce. A Woman. Tower Publications, Inc., 1961 (Box 6)
- Ellis, Joan. Lana. Tower Publications, Inc., 1960 (Box 7)
- Ellis, Joan. Sugar And Spice. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 7)
- Ellis, Joan. High School Hellion. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 7)
- Ellis, Joan. Hip Chick. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 8)
- Ellis, Joan. Don't Tell Anyone. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Fairbank, Walton. Houseboy. Pyramid Books, 1956 (Box 6)
- Falcone, John. Restless Women. Wizard Publications, 1967 (Box 1)
- Fickling, G.G.. Sex Pit. Softcover Library, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- Fischer, Bruno. So Wicked My Love. Fawcett Publications, Inc., 1961 (Box 4)
- Foran, Steve. Slave Vixens. Stardust Readers, 1964 (Box 9)
- Ford, Robert B.. Emerald Bikini, The. Saber Books, 1963 (Box 8)
- Frame, Bart. Indiscretions of a French Model. Croydon Publishing Company, 1953 (Box 9)
- Friday, Nancy. Forbidden Flowers: More Women's Sexual Fantasies. Pocket Books, 1975 (Box 1)
- Friedman, Stuart. Irina. Monarch Books, Inc., 1963 (Box 7)
- Fulton, Ward. Sorority Sex Freak. Brandon Books, 1976 (Box 1)
- Gaddis, Peggy. Lulie. Belmont Productions, Inc., 1962 (Box 6)
- Garve, Andrew. The End of the Track. Berkley Books, 1955 (Box 4)
- George, Irving. Madison Avenue Nympho. Art Enterprises, Inc., 1962 (Box 5)
- Goff, Jerry M.. Tropic of Carla. Camerarts Publishing Co., Inc. (Box 6)
- Gold, R.C.. Drive-In Girl. Tower Publications, 1961 (Box 9)
- Grayson, Roger. A Christmas Party. Tiburon House Publishing Co., 1970 (Box 1)
- Gunnell, Kenneth. The Graduate Mistress. Venus Library, 1971 (Box 2)
- Hale, Laura. Lessons In Lust. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1961 (Box 6)
- Hall, Oakley. So Many Doors. Bantam Books, Inc., 1959 (Box 5)
- Hamilton, Greg. Little Girl Lost. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 6)
- Hamilton, Greg. Honey Child. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 7)
- Hamilton, Greg. That Kind Of Wife. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 8)
- Hampton, Stella. Dark Quarters. Fabian Books, 1959 (Box 8)
- Harding, Steve. Young Temptresses, The. Medco Books, 1967 (Box 9)
- Harland, Tom. Insatiable. Softcover Library, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- Harper, Daniel, ed.. Nymphets, The. Lancer Books, Inc., 1963 (Box 7)
- Harris, Amy. Forever Amy. Tower Publications, 1962 (Box 6)
- Haskell, Frank. Young Doctor. Star Guidance, Inc., 1954 (Box 9)
- Hastings, March. Chico's Women. Tower Publications, Inc., 1962 (Box 7)
- Hastings, March. The Demands of the Flesh. Newsstand Library Incorporated, 1959 (Box 10)
- Hayes, John. One Hot Afternoon. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1967 (Box 6)
- Hayes, John. Midnight Mistress. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Heimer, Mel. Girl In Murder Flat, The. Fawcett Publications, Inc., 1955 (Box 5)
- Henry, George. Tasting Passion. Cameo Library, 1975 (Box 2)
- Hesse, Hildegard. College of Lust. Maverick Publishing Co., 1978 (Box 2)
- Hitt, Orrie. Suburban Wife. Universal Publishing & Distributing Corporation, 1958 (Box 5)
- Hitt, Orrie. Summer Of Sin. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1964 (Box 6)
- Hitt, Orrie. As Bad As They Come. Tower Publications, 1959 (Box 6)
- Hitt, Orrie. Teaser. Lancer Books, Inc., 1956 (Box 6)
- Hitt, Orrie. Love Season, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1961 (Box 7)
- Hitt, Orrie. Torrid Wench. Kozy Books, Inc., 1963 (Box 7)
- Hitt, Orrie. Color Of Lust, The. Lancer Books, Inc., 1964 (Box 7)
- Hitt, Orrie. Torrid Teens, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1960 (Box 7)
- Hitt, Orrie. Ex-Virgin. Universal Publishing and Distributing Company, 1963 (Box 7)
- Hitt, Orrie. I Prowl By Night. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1961 (Box 8)
- Hitt, Orrie. Peeper, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1959 (Box 8)
- Hitt, Orrie. Two Of A Kind. Tower Publications, 1960 (Box 8)
- Hitt, Orrie. I'll Call Every Monday. Vantage Press, Inc., 1953 (Box 8)
- Holland, Kel. Strange Young Wife, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1963 (Box 6)
- Hollander, Xaviera. The Happy Hooker: My Own Story. Dell Publishing Co., 1972 (Box 2)
- Hollander, Xaviera. Letters to the Happy Hooker. Warner Paperback, 1973 (Box 2)
- Howard, Munroe. Call Me Brick. Dell Publishing Co., 1967 (Box 3)
- Howard, Munroe. Call Him Rod. Dell Publishing Co., Inc., 1972 (Box 10)
- Huish, Leonard. Window, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1961 (Box 8)
- Hunter, Paul. Black Teen Nymph. Eros Publishing, 1975 (Box 2)
- Hytes, Jason. Jailbait. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 5)
- Hytes, Jason. Immoral. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 6)
- Hytes, Jason. Split Level Sin. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 7)
- Hytes, Jason. Perfumed. Tower Publications, Inc., 1963 (Box 9)
- Hytes, Jason. Wild Week, The. Tower Publications, Inc., 1963 (Box 9)
- James, Bobijo. The Neighbors' Little Boys. Surrey House, Inc., 1974 (Box 10)
- Jackson, Byron. The Coeds Torment. American Art Enterprises, 1977 (Box 3)
- James, Scotti. In the Greek Fashion. E.L. Publishing Co., 1969 (Box 2)
- James, Terry. Professor's Wife, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1962 (Box 8)
- Jeffy, Eamon. Too Hot To Handle. All Star Books, 1964 (Box 9)
- Jennings, John. Sea Eagles, The. Permabooks, 1951 (Box 5)
- Johnston, William. A Man In Her House. Tower Publications, 1962 (Box 8)
- Jones, George E.. Trap. Graphic Publishing Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 5)
- Kahler, Jack. Sex Frame. Private Edition Books, 1964 (Box 9)
- Kamins, Jeanette. Everything But A Husband. Dell Publishing Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 8)
- Kane, Frank. The Mourning After. Dell Publishing Co., Inc., 1961 (Box 10)
- Keller, Dan. Flee The Night In Anger. Popular Library, 1954 (Box 5)
- Kemp, Kimberly. Forbidden. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 6)
- Kramer, George. School For Girls. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1953 (Box 8)
- Kramer, Gerald. Coming Of Age. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Kramer, Gerald. Come Be My Slave. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Larry "The Silver Fox". My Life with Xaviera, "The Happy Hooker". Warner Books, Inc., 1974 (Box 2)
- Lindsey, Todd. The Boss's Daughter. Cameo Library, 1975 (Box 2)
- Loomis, Rae. Luisita. Ace Books, Inc., 1954 (Box 4)
- Lord, Sheldon. A Woman Must Love. Tower Publications, 1960 (Box 5)
- Lord, Sheldon. A Special Kind Of Love. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1963 (Box 9)
- Louya, Pierre. Woman And The Puppet. Avon Publishing Co., Inc., 1951 (Box 5)
- Lynch, Ben. Payment for Pleasure. Newsstand International, Ltd, 1965 (Box 2)
- Mahler, Helen A.. Empress of Byzantium. Bantam Books, Inc., 1953 (Box 5)
- Malaponte, Marco. New Man In The House. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1963 (Box 7)
- Mallord, Cory. Call Me Kitten. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Mare, Lilith della. Everyone's Slave. Carlyle Communications, 1975 (Box 2)
- Mark, Ted. Back Home At The O.R.G.Y.. Berkley Medallion, 1968 (Box 2)
- Marmor, Arnold. Forbidden Flesh. Art Enterprises, Inc., 1962 (Box 6)
- Marnais, Philip. Saigon After Dark. Macfadden-Bartell Corporation, 1967 (Box 10)
- Marshall, Alan. Man Hungry. Tower Publications, 1959 (Box 5)
- Martin, George Victor. Evil That Men Do, The. Berkley Publishing Corp., 1958 (Box 6)
- Mayflower, Nina. The Washington Sex Scandal. Candid Books, 1976 (Box 2)
- Mayo, Dallas. Craving, The. Tower Publications, Inc., 1962 (Box 5)
- Mayo, Dallas. Kitten. Tower Publications, Inc., 1961 (Box 7)
- Mayo, Dallas. All Together Now. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- McCartney, Mickey. The Groupie Grope. Eros Publishing Co., 1976 (Box 2)
- McCoy, Dean. Double Up. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1961 (Box 9)
- Michaelson, John Nairne. Morning, Winter, and Night. Berkley Publishing Corp., 1958 (Box 7)
- Miller, George. A Classroom Disgrace. Tiburon Publishing House, 1974 (Box 2)
- Mitchell, Julian. A Disturbing Influence. Petty & Sons, Ltd, 1962 (Box 2)
- Moore, William. Not So Innocent. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 7)
- Morehead, Jeff. Forced to Please. Carlyle Communications, 1977 (Box 3)
- Namban, Akahige. Yakuza Perfume. Blue Moon Books, 1992 (Box 3)
- Nelson, Connie. Lady Of Leisure. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Nelson, Connie. Daytime Lovers. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Nelson, Connie. Voluptuary, The. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- Nesbit, Malcom. Chariot of Flesh. Olympia Press, 1955 (Box 3)
- Newbury, Will. Tourist Trap. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- North, Kay. Silk Sheets. Newsstand International, Ltd., 1965 (Box 3)
- O'Bannon, Brian. Thrill Hungry. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- Omarr, Sydney. My Bed Has Echoes. Fabian Books Publications, 1957 (Box 9)
- Owen, Jack. The Beach Bums. Signet Books, 1959 (Box 3)
- Ozaki, Milton. Dressed To Kill. Graphic Publishing Company, Inc., 1956 (Box 5)
- Parks, Joseph. Oral Outings. (Box 4)
- Pendleton, John. A Helpful Nurse. Briarcliff Books, 1977 (Box 3)
- Pierce, Wade. Uncertain Destiny. Vega Books, Inc., 1962 (Box 6)
- Porter, Gil. Coupled. Essex House, 1968 (Box 10)
- Prather, Richard S.. Lie Down, Killer. Fawcett Publications, Inc., 1961 (Box 8)
- Pratt, Theodore. Handsome's Seven Women. Fawcett World Library, 1959 (Box 6)
- Price, Marjorie. Trick Or Treat. Tower Publications, Inc., 1964 (Box 7)
- Price, Marjorie. Anything Goes. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Pruett, Herbert O.. Her Mother's Lover. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1962 (Box 8)
- Reach, James. Innocent One, The. Popular Library, 1954 (Box 5)
- Richards, Rick. Abnormal. Tower Publications, Inc., 1962 (Box 6)
- Roberts, Herb. Motel Mismates. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1962 (Box 7)
- Roberts, Herb. These Women. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1963 (Box 8)
- Roberts, Herbert. Early Fruit. Softcover Library, Inc., 1966 (Box 7)
- Roberts, Lee. Little Sister. Fawcett Publications, Inc., 1956 (Box 5)
- Roget, Alexis. Man Bait. Chariot, 1962 (Box 9)
- Roote, Leslie. Fair Exchange. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Roote, Leslie. Go-Go Girls, The. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Rouville, Claude. Summer Spice. Berkley Publishing Corporation, 1962 (Box 6)
- Royal, D.. I, Virgin. Fleur De Lis Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 8)
- Royer, Louis-Charles. The Flesh. Pyramid Publications, Inc., 1962 (Box 10)
- Russo, Paul V.. Stag Starlet. Tower Publications, 1961 (Box 6)
- Russo, Paul V.. A Touch Of Depravity. Tower Publications, Inc., 1960 (Box 7)
- Savage, Jack. Torture Love-Cage. Novel Books, Inc., 1959 (Box 5)
- Saxon, John. Pleasure Girl. Phoenix Press, 1938 (Box 5)
- Sellers, Con. Miss Warmflesh. Novel Books, Inc., 1964 (Box 7)
- Serra, Art. Lament For A Virgin. Tower Publications, Inc., 1961 (Box 6)
- Shaffer, Terry. Teen-Age Mischief. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 7)
- Shaffer, Terry. Young And Restless. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Sherman, Joan. Suzy. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1960 (Box 5)
- Short, Betty. Rambling Maids, The. Fabian Books, 1959 (Box 6)
- Smith, L.K.. Silk & Satin Mistress. Star Distributors Ltd., 1977 (Box 3)
- Smith, Robert Paul. Time and the Place. Avon Publications Inc., 1952 (Box 5)
- Sorenson, W.. London Sex Sweepstakes. Eros Publishing, 1976 (Box 3)
- St. James, Blakely. Christina's Bliss. Playboy Paperbacks, 1981 (Box 3)
- St. James, Blakely. Christina's Island. Playboy Paperbacks, 1982 (Box 3)
- St. James, Blakely. Christina's Rapture. Playboy, 1978 (Box 3)
- St. John, Burton. One Touch Of Satin. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1964 (Box 6)
- St. Laurent, Cecil. Affairs Of Caroline Cherie, The. Dell Publishing Company, Inc., 1954 (Box 7)
- Stevens, Gus. Three Easy Lessons. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Stevens, Toni. Never Let Me Go. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Stevens, Toni. Private Pleasures. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Stokes, Manning. Girl On A Couch. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1961 (Box 7)
- Stout, Rex. How Like A God. Lion Books, Inc., 1955 (Box 4)
- Swenson, ,Peggy. Unloved, The. Tower Publications, Inc., 1961 (Box 9)
- Sydney, Cynthia. Stay Until Morning. Midwood Enterprises, Inc., 1966 (Box 7)
- Sydney, Cynthia. Lost And Found. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Thompson, John B.. Sinful Virgin. Arco Publishing Company, Inc., 1952 (Box 5)
- Torres, Tereska. Golden Cage, The. Avon Book Division, 1959 (Box 8)
- Tresillian, Richard. Blood of the Bond-master. Warner Books, 1977 (Box 3)
- Tryon, Mark. Sinning Lens, The. Berkley Publishing Corp., 1956 (Box 7)
- Turner, John. Christine. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Turney, Catherine. Other One, The. Dell Publishing Company, Inc., 1952 (Box 5)
- Upton, Jack. Passion Nightmare. Target Novels, 1964 (Box 7)
- Various. The Best of Beeline. Carlyle Communications, 1985 (Box 2)
- Various. This Is My Body. Berkley Publishing Corp., 1957 (Box 9)
- Vassi, Marco. The Wonderful World Of Penthouse Sex. Warner Books, 1975 (Box 3)
- Veach, Charlton. Toby's Tricks. Carlyle Communications Inc., 1974 (Box 2)
- Wallace, Wolf. Watcher, The. Softcover Library, Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
- Ward, Alice. Two Woman Team. Eros Publishing, 1978 (Box 3)
- Warren, Paul. Next Time Is For Life. Dell Publishing Company, Inc, 1953 (Box 5)
- Weingarten, Violet. A Woman of Feeling. Dell Publishing Co., 1971 (Box 3)
- Wellman, Paul I.. Iron Mistress, The. Pocket Books, Inc., 1953 (Box 5)
- Wendell, Matthew. Slit Circus. Aquarius 7 Publishers, 1972 (Box 3)
- West, C.P.. Party, Party. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- West, Edwin. Brother And Sister. Monarch Books, Inc., 1961 (Box 8)
- West, Nathanael. Miss Lonelyhearts. Avon Publications, Inc., 1933 (Box 5)
- West, Rona. The Hot Ones. Carlyle Communications Inc., 1974 (Box 2)
- Williams, Jeffrey. Dutch Treat. Tower Publications, Inc., 1966 (Box 9)
- Willow, Peter. Enforced Respect. Wee Hours, 1968 (Box 3)
- Winters, Dee. Offshore Resort. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1962 (Box 8)
- Wood, Clement. Studio Affair. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1951 (Box 8)
- Wood, Clement. Desire. Berkley Publishing Corp., 1950 (Box 9)
- Woodford, Jack. Woman Of Algiers. Firmac Publications, 1962 (Box 6)
- Woods, Merry. Small Town Sinner. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- Woods, Merry. One For All. Tower Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 9)
- Woodward, L.T.. Deceivers, The. Universal Publishing and Distributing Corporation, 1962 (Box 6)
- Woolfe, Byron. Never Enough. Saber Books, 1959 (Box 9)
- Friday, John. Chained, Whipped Librarians. Greenleaf Classics, 1984 (Box 9)
- Hawkins, Bob. Librarian with the Hots. Greenleaf Classics, 1986 (Box 9)
- Silvers, Nathan. A Librarian Enslaved. Greenleaf Classics, 1986 (Box 9)
- Silvers, Nathan. Lash the Librarian!. Greenleaf Classics, 1987 (Box 9)